[
    {
        "id": "1",
        "question": "Which planet is nearest to the sun?",
        "choices": [
            "Mercury",
            "Pluto",
            "Mars",
            "Venus"],
        "answer": "Mercury"
    },
    {
        "id": "2",
        "question": "What is the largest planet in the solar system?",
        "choices": [
            "Saturn",
            "Uranus",
            "Neptune",
            "Jupiter"],
        "answer": "Jupiter"
    },
    {
        "id": "3",
        "question": "Between which planets do you find the Asteroid Belt?",
        "choices": [
            "Venus and Earth",
            "Earth and Mars",
            "Mars and Jupiter",
            "Jupiter and saturn"],
        "answer": "Mars and Jupiter"
    },
    {
        "id": "4",
        "question": "What is the name of the largest object in the Asteroid Belt?",
        "choices": [
            "Eris",
            "Ceres",
            "Juno",
            "Hygiea"],
        "answer": "Ceres"
    },
    {
        "id": "5",
        "question": "Now Pluto has been downgraded as a planet, which planet is the furthest from the sun?",
        "choices": [
            "Uranus",
            "Jupiter",
            "Neptune",
            "Venus"],
        "answer": "Neptune"
    },
    {
        "id": "6",
        "question": "How many known planets are there?",
        "choices": [
            "Seven",
            "Ten",
            "Eight",
            "Nine"],
        "answer": "Eight"
    },
    {
        "id": "7",
        "question": "How many of these are known as gas giants?",
        "choices": [
            "One",
            "Two",
            "Three",
            "Four"],
        "answer": "Four"
    },
    {
        "id": "8",
        "question": "Umbriel is a moon of which planet?",
        "choices": [
            "Saturn",
            "Neptune",
            "Uranus",
            "Jupiter"],
        "answer": "Uranus"
    },
    {
        "id": "9",
        "question": "How many moons orbit Mars?",
        "choices": [
            "One",
            "Two",
            "Three",
            "Four"],
        "answer": "Two"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "Which of these is a moon of Mars?",
        "choices": [
            "Makemake",
            "Io",
            "Europa",
            "Phobos"],
        "answer": "Phobos"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "Pluto is the largest object in which part of the solar system?",
        "choices": [
            "Kuiper Belt",
            "Gas Giants",
            "Inner Planets",
            "Oort Cloud"],
        "answer": "Kuiper Belt"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "Which of these is not a moon of Pluto?",
        "choices": [
            "Charon",
            "Hydra",
            "Io",
            "Nix"],
        "answer": "Io"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "Which planet is famous for its large rings?",
        "choices": [
            "Venus",
            "Neptune",
            "Uranus",
            "Saturn"],
        "answer": "Saturn"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "Which of the planets is thought to have the warmest climate?",
        "choices": [
            "Mars",
            "Venus",
            "Mercury",
            "Earth"],
        "answer": "Venus"
    },
    {
        "id": "15",
        "question": "After the sun, which is the nearest star to the solar system at four light years?",
        "choices": [
            "Proxima Centauri",
            "Betelgeuse",
            "Bernards Star",
            "VY Canis Majoris"],
        "answer": "Proxima Centauri"
    },
    {
        "id": "16",
        "question": "The solar system is a part of which galaxy?",
        "choices": [
            "The Sombrero Galaxy",
            "Andromeda",
            "Hoags Object",
            "Milky Way"],
        "answer": "Milky Way"
    },
    {
        "id": "17",
        "question": "Approximately how old is the solar system thought to be?",
        "choices": [
            "7.5 Billion Years",
            "6 Billion Years",
            "4.5 Billion Years",
            "3 Billion Years"],
        "answer": "4.5 Billion Years"
    },
    {
        "id": "18",
        "question": "When the moon passes across the sun and blocks the daylight, this is called a solar...",
        "choices": [
            "Eclipse",
            "System",
            "Storm",
            "Flair"],
        "answer": "Eclipse"
    },
    {
        "id": "19",
        "question": "What is Makemake?",
        "choices": [
            "Inner Planet",
            "Object in the Asteroid Belt",
            "There is no such object",
            "Object in the Kuiper Belt"],
        "answer": "Object in the Kuiper Belt"
    },
    {
        "id": "20",
        "question": "Name a famous comet from our solar system?",
        "choices": [
            "Halley's",
            "Ceres",
            "Eris",
            "Callisto"],
        "answer": "Halley's"
    }
]
